Luis Grau

Senior Software Engineer

(609) 568-0106

 \sim

luisgrau-biz@outlook.com

About Me

Bringing more than 7 years of experience leading website design projects, including gathering user requirements, producing code, creating mockups and enhancing designs. Focused on creating clean, robust code with exceptional security. Achieves compatibility targets while meeting and exceeding customer demands.

PER SKILLS

Agile Workflow

Programming

Front End Web Development

HTML

CSS

React

Angular

Javascript

UX/UI

Software Best Practices

Web App Development

EDUCATION



2013-09 - 2016-07 Bache

Bachelor of Science

Computer Science And Programming

Seoul National University of Science And Technology - Seoul, Korea

2016-11 - 2018-07 Bachelor of Science

Computer Programming

Pace University - Seidenberg School of Computer Science and Information Systems

EXPERIENCE

2019-06 - Current Web Developer

Topta

- Provided front-end website development using WordPress, Hubspot and other editing software.
- Planned website development, converting mockups into usable web presence with HTML, JavaScript, AJAX and JSON coding.
- Coded websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and jQuery languages.
- Ran debugging tools to eliminate flaws and glitches prior to publishing.
- Applied emerging technologies to update and maintain site applicability.
- Collaborated with stakeholders during development processes to confirm creative proposals and design best practices.
- Assembled and addressed technical and design requirements, integrating user-facing and front-end elements to maintain web presence effectiveness.

2018-11 - 2019-03 Web Developer

Mapbox, San Francisco, CA

- Collaborated with stakeholders during development processes to confirm creative proposals and design best practices.
- Assembled and addressed technical and design requirements, integrating user-facing and front-end elements to maintain web presence effectiveness.
- Followed SDLC best practices within Agile environment to produce rapid iterations for clients.
- Authored reusable content modules and developed prototypes.

2016-09 - 2017-12 Intern

Wantedlab, Inc, Seoul, Korea

- Answered and transferred incoming telephone calls, taking messages for various staff members.
- Sorted, organized and maintained files.
- Followed school and classroom policies, regulations, dress codes and schedules.